也许是我对这段友情疏于照顾了
Maybe I've been neglecting our friendship.
佩妮知道我和我妈关系复杂
Penny knows I have a complicated relationship with my mother;
可她却毫不在意
it's like she doesn't even care.
实验室里事多繁杂
And with everything going on at the lab
加上还要计划婚礼
and planning the wedding,
我的空闲时间实在太少了
I just, I have so little free time.
佩妮不知道我妈有多会玩弄人于鼓掌之间
Penny doesn't know how manipulative my mother can be.
你知道世界上所谓的
Did you know there's such a thing as
逆反再逆反之三重逆反心理学吗
reverse, reverse, reverse psychology?
因为...  真的有
Because... there is.
她一定觉得自己受冷落了
I mean, she must feel so abandoned.
她太习惯我在她左右
She's used to me being there all the time,
但我现在有了自己的生活
but now I have my own life,
她只能自己适应这件事
and she's just gonna have to accept it.
为什么我妈为佩妮骄傲  而不是为我骄傲
And why is my mom proud of Penny and not me?
最重要的问题是  为什么佩妮不愿意
I mean, the real question is: why is Penny so afraid of me